We Are The Champions   - Queen
Lyrics Freddie Mercury
Composed Freddie Mercury
I've paid my dues
Time after time
I've done my sentence
But committed no crime
And bad mistakes
I've made a few
I've had my share of sand kicked in my face
But I've come through
And I need to go on and on and on and on
We are the champions my friends
And we'll keep on fighting 'til the end
We are the champions
No time for losers
'Cause we are the champions
Of the world
I've taken my bows
And my curtain calls
You brought me fame and fortune and everything that goes with it
I thank you all
But it's been no bed of roses
No pleasure cruise
I consider it a challenge before the whole human race
And I ain't gonna lose
And I need to go on and on and on and on
We are the champions my friends
And we'll keep on fighting 'til the end
We are the champions
No time for losers
'Cause we are the champions
Of the world
We are the champions my friends
And we'll keep on fighting 'til the end oh
We are the champions
No time for losers
'Cause we are the champions